webstore.com 2011-12-31

# Webstore.com News

|  |  Adv   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  

|  | 

Scope

Webstore has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as 

an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us using the [Contact Us](http://www.webstore.com/support.php?a=add) form. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on Webstore. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on October 8, 2009.

Collection

You can browse Webstore without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States.

We may collect and store the following personal information such as:

email address, physical contact information such as mailing address and phone; transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as bidding, buying, selling, item and content you generate or that relates to your account); shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item; dispute resolution, correspondence through our website, and correspondence sent to us; other information from your interaction with our website, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information; additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity or ownership of an item you list); information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data; and other supplemental information from third parties (for example, if you incur a debt to Webstore, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law).

Marketing

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our ad-customization programs, simply indicate your preference in your Webstore Members Area or by following the unsubscribe directions provided with the communication or advertisement.

Use

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: provide the services and customer support you request;

resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;

customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;

tell you about our services and those of our corporate family, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

Our Disclosure of Your Information

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: provide the services and customer support you request;

resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;

customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;

tell you about our services and those of our corporate family, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

Information You Share on Webstore

Your User ID is displayed throughout Webstore (and so available to the public), and is connected to all of your Webstore activity. Other people can see your bids, purchases, items for sale, storefronts, ratings and associated comments. Notices sent to other community members about suspicious activity and policy violations on our sites refer to User IDs and specific items. So if you associate your name with your User ID, the people to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify your Webstore activities.

If you access our sites from a shared computer or a computer in an internet café, certain information about you, such as your User ID, activity or reminders from Webstore, may also be visible to other individuals who use the computer after you.

Using Information from Webstore

Webstore enables you to share personal information to complete transactions. We encourage you to disclose your privacy practices and respect the privacy of other users. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information and therefore we encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your trading partner before entering into a transaction and choosing to share your information. To help protect your privacy, we allow only limited access to other users' contact, shipping and financial information to facilitate your transactions. When users are involved in a transaction, they may have access to each other's name, User ID, email address and other contact and shipping information. In all cases, you must give other users a chance to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them.

You agree to use user information only for:

Webstore transaction-related purposes that are not unsolicited commercial messages;

using services offered through Webstore (e.g. escrow, insurance, shipping and fraud complaints), or other purposes that a user expressly chooses.

Cookies

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. For more information about why we use cookies, see Cookies, Web Beacons, and Your Privacy.

A few important things you should know about cookies are that:

We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies.

We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status and these cookies are not tied to personal information. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services. You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the sites that we do not control. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page.)

No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing

We and our users do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your Webstore notification preferences so we communicate to you as you prefer. You are not licensed to add other Webstore users, even a user who has purchased an item from you, to your mailing list (email or physical mail) without their express consent. To report Webstore-related spam or spoof emails to Webstore, please forward the email to postmaster@Webstore.com. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content, but we do not permanently store messages sent through these tools. If you send an email to an email address that is not registered in our community, we do not permanently store that email or use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses.

Account Protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your Webstore password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Webstore and change your password.

Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to your Webstore account and changing your information online. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Webstore User Agreement, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

If you post comments on a transaction or a review on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by the general public, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in transaction comments.

Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our website or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Webstore does not control the privacy policies of third parties or third party web sites accessible through Webstore, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a prominent notice of material changes on our homepage as well as the privacy policy page. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the site. In addition, we will notify you through the Webstore Message Board. If your questions are not answered online, you may contact us using the [Contact Us](http://www.webstore.com/support.php?a=add) form.  

* * *

---|---|---  
  
Copyright ©1996-2011 **[Webstore.com](http://www.webstore.com/)**. All Rights Reserved. Designated trademarks and brands are the property of their respective owners. Use of this Web site constitutes acceptance of the **Webstore** [TERMS & CONDITIONS](http://www.webstore.com/terms,page,content_pages) and [PRIVACY POLICY](http://www.webstore.com/privacy,page,content_pages)

Page generated in 0.348164 seconds
